I'm proud of my age, 1997. You're old
.  He's not old yet, just a
commenter.  You're 28, not
30,
your attitude is really a compliment
to your feelings.  Guys, welcome to one of the
biggest parts of my childhood,
Campo Rizal.  Because our challenge
today is still a challenge.
Okay, just an easy basic one.
An easy basic.  Easy and basic.
Easy basic check.  That's not it yet
.
Woohoo.
What is that?  Why are you so kind here?
Church.
What do
you want us to do here?
I'll take them to where we eat here at
La Plaza.  This is where we
hang out most often.  Here we eat frying
saucer and then mommy.  Taste it, guys.
How much is high school?  Shin
ph5 now 15 now.
What's the problem?
This is how it is.   Let
's eat one of the most
proud things of our state, Quezon.  The
golden jade shopaw.  Delicious, guys.  Look at
how much meat there is.  You can watch this at
7:00.  I'll find the shop.
You are eating it, not eating it, he said,
why won't you eat it?
You can eat it so we can find out
why he won't eat it.
You already know that a crab is a
crab or a crab's lover. You are a crab
Hi, my friends.
Mitch already knows this.  I don't have an intro yet.
Hey team shas.
Just a pinch of pinch.
Hi guys, we are the group five.  Hello!
Now guys, we will take you on a tour of
our provinces and in this vlog,
the first place we will go is where I
grew up, my province,
Ationa
province city.
Oh, the city.
Hey,
okay, let's get started.
Hi guys, I just wanted to update you that
we are heading to the first place that
teacher always goes to.  This
should have been taught in elementary
school, guys.  Nothing.  Okay.  This was my
elementary school, but since
my high school is closed, we're moving to a new school.
Ah, that's why I thought Tarant was closed.   It's
just close.  You were
just walking around as a child.
walk
why
why are they running over me because there are many people
crossing
yes the
fare was only four at that time
let's talk about age ah
why am I proud of my age 1997
ah you are old
he is not old yet sorry he is
only a year old he
doesn't speak 1998 also because
he is like 2004 what not
comment you are 28 not
your behavior really looks like the youngest
pangaby really to be honest.
Yes.  If you don't float, you're a soup.  If
you're not a soup, you're a menudo.
That's a dish.  What's that,
guys? Or is that why there are festivals like that?
Those flags are the test.  Or
let's have the tagultol tagult fishing
festival.  Live
differently, the music is not like that.  We guys have our own
song for the Tagult fishing
festival.
I'm not laughing at myself, I'm laughing at
myself, I always go through this guys,
we're going to Atimonan Central School
or what we call Campo Rizal, this is
elementary school, but because there's a part here that's
high school, this is where I was, guys, I used to
run around when I was a majorette,
so this part is
elementary, this part is high school, it
feels like
it's gone, guys, let's go down, what's the
torch there,
wow,
wow, guys, welcome to one of the
biggest parts of my hood, Campo
Rizal.
There's an
elementary school, but this
building is the same size as this high school, but it
became my classroom.  The only
classroom I've ever had was on site, so it was
difficult to climb up there.  So let's
just leave it here.  The Tagultol Festival takes place here
.  I'm also throwing batons here,
so I have a baton with me today
because our challenge today
still has a challenge.  You should try to
accept what you are doing with a stick.
Because that's what I did when
I was in high school, when I was a kid.  Now
you will try to do that.
Yes.  Okay.  Okay.  Just an easy basic
.
An easy basic.  An easy
basic.  Easy and basic.  Easy and basic.  Or just
like this, it's an
easy basic check, it's not like that,
what are you doing,
he got it right in 2 seconds,
criminology
Wow!  That's so high.
There's a bit here.  There's a bit more here.  Ah,
char, that's
not a ball.  You won't argue.
Okayfly.
High butterfly.  There he is, guys.  Before,
guys.  Group 5 is said to have died from the reaction of
group 5.
One more thing.  One more thing, love.  One more thing.
Wow!
Nothing yet.
Yoo!  Here is the look.
Go, baby.  Show them
your fierce skills.  Oh, when there's a ball.
Following the ball is a child.  Next to
Cherny Boy is a ball.  Isn't it?  No.
Me too.  Me too.   I
love the difficulty,
yeah, I said
I can't stand the cold anymore and
I'm losing my hair like before, guys.
I just learned about it from the
cheat majority I used to follow.
I'm split.
Yes.  But now guys, this is how it is.
Follow me, idols.  Here we are
at the grand stands forward.  You're a forum because you're
only one line.
What is that?  Arms forward group five.
School tour.  Guys, this is our grand
stand.
Woohoo!
Oh!
Oh my gosh.  This is the view of it.  When
you're seated here, this is
his view.  It's beautiful, look at the trees
there.  There are so many things.  It's okay
.  Thank you, Sister Monan Quezon, for
keeping the color green
.  There's a
public game today, guys.
Tower oh d children oh.  Every child
we have, Chenny doesn't.
Okay.  Or next time.  What I want to know is
where you are going when you enter.
I didn't cut.  I didn't
cut anything but I went home right away.
I wasn't really always involved in
organizations like that in high school.
SSD, what
officer am I? I always ask everyone I
can join. Will I join?  This is
what that drum is.  Okay for our
place.  Let's go to where we often
hang out, near the church.  Let's go.
Let's go.  The one you hang out with at church.
You're out of church.  The duck that is
called.
Guys, we're here.  We're at the church
where the teacher hangs out when there's
no class.  That's it.  One, two.
Thank you guys.  Thank you.
I don't see it.  We're here, guys, at the
church.  The mass is running.
But this is because we are here in the duck, this is where
my classmates and I hang out in
this area.  That's where we
hang out.  It's like we're on a fil trip,
guys, here in Amitonan, Quezon Province.
Whenever I have a fight, I'm like
that.  I have a fight.  Tomorrow.
I always go to church in this small part
of town.  I used to be a very religious person
.  I used to work in a choir.
What is that?  Why are you so kind here?
Church.
What do you want when we're not here?
That's it.  I don't have much
else to hang out with.  You're
really very kind to that child.  Because the
billiards are the ones that are
tickling, the billiards that you drink are the ones that
we didn't do, you didn't do it,
you go there when you nod, my situation is that
you don't have that, guys, because when
I was in high school, I was the eldest, so
I used to piss off my parents.
I must be a student.  I'm one of those people who
always has an award, and his mother also said that
he was a teacher for Santo Niño.  Either now
or it's hard to joke about that.  Go ahead.   Okay, okay, it's
not a blessing,
what kind of food trip are you eating here or taking it out? Let's go grab some
food, everyone, let's
go.  I'll take them to where
we eat.  Let's eat.  Yes,
food trips are like that.  If it's close to the
church, there are restaurants there.
Guys, our church is beautiful.
Yes, right here in
your church, the
baby is going to be banged.  That's it,
you're making a video, not the one that causes a collision, okay?
That's different.  Wait, this is one of
my favorite high school guys.
There you go.  Because there are 35 of us
here at La Plaza.  This is where
we hang out most often.  We're eating
fried food here and mom is very close.   They say we
eat while
flying on a
flying saucer.  It turns out there are only six.  Just
try it guys.
Taste it, guys.  This is the sharp
heat.
Wow, that's delicious.
How much is high school?
PH5 is now
15, inflation is real.  Let
's eat some isaw because it's one of
my favorites.
I need that sofa badly.
One of my favorites.
What's the problem?  Just like this
.
I should eat profish.  Hi, is
there potato fish?  There is hot dog fish.
They're delicious.
Now we're going to the
province because we've recovered.
We're heading to the test
province, let's continue.  We are going to the
municipality of Atimonan, Quezon in
Tagultol.  Fishing festival.  Long live,
guys.  Now we are here in the municipality
of Atimonan, Quezon.  If
you notice, there are still designs because
the Tagult fishing festival has just ended
and we haven't been able to go because
we have projects.  But that's it, let's eat
one of the most proud things of Atim
Monan, Quezon.  The Golden J Shopa, but
we already ate yesterday.  Yes,
you liked him, so I liked
him because he's golden J Shopaw.  That's it
.  Do you like it?  Who wants?
Delicious, guys.
Shopaw with cheese.  Delicious, guys.
Look at the abundance of flesh.
Lots of space.
Mmm.
Look at this, guys.
What time can they be watched?
You can watch this at 7:00.  Look for a
shop.  Mm.  7-Eleven is
7-Eleven.  I'm full.  I'm going to play,
guys.  It's really delicious here, so
I can't really trust it anymore because
in Vietnam, wherever Vietnam is
delicious, you should go, you go everywhere, it's
delicious like that in
Vietnam.
No, sister Mon, sister Mon, I thought she was
Vietnamese.  Let's go.
I'm tired for my sister.
He was still holding the bamboo.  This is Sister
Monang.  This is Sister Monang.  That's why she's
Sister Monan.  Sister Monang.  Do you know my
sister first?   They say
you have nothing to worry about.  I'm sorry
.
They said they would make a video in the back.  They know
this behind the scenes.   It's
nice here.  Look at this, guys.  No
guys, we're here at Bay Park now.
In our time, this didn't exist yet.  This isn't
this beautiful.  That's just how it is
.  That's just how it is.  Now of course, we are
evolving and
upgrading,
guys, now all the land you saw is
ours, there is no land, water, that is
not ours, boy, they are
eating it, they are not eating it, they
say,
why won't they eat it?
You can eat it so we can find out
why they won't eat it, of
course, give me an
explanation, as long as it's not
poison, then
give me an explanation, as
if the one you just mentioned is your relative, where is the
kalakukoy?  How do you know if
a crab is a crab lover or
a crab lover?   Very specific
.
My lover's head is pounded again by a crab
so he won't eat it.
Yes, because I'm
in love with you,
Cabbets,
and there are many places you can
hang out.
Mm.  If you just want to reset it,
that's it.  I hope the camera isn't too late
.  We will not reset.
I don't have a reset button anymore.  You can
even take a screenshot.  What is a screenshot?
Nothing.  I just want to.  What?
There's no entry yet, are you ready to enter?   There's something else
.  There's still a little bit
left.  What is a screenshot?  Maybe go with
this and then that's it.  Don't do it.
We have walked.  Oh, it's so good
that we can't be screenshotted.  The
air is not good when you arrive in Quezon.
What a little trouble you had earlier.  Yes.
He actually treated her
like the one who hit the motorcycle.
But look at Chen's outfit
.  That's what high
school outfits used to be like.
Offlw.
No.  This is serious.  My grandfather was like that
when he was a tricycle driver.  There you go.
Yes.  There you go.  You have a grandfather.
Oh,
but my grandfather's slippers aren't like that
.
He is the one who doesn't get pregnant.
Your slippers are really dirty there.
There are crabs, baby.  Oh.  There they are,
the lovers, the
cbets, it turns out that the
teacher's passion was cbets,
when he was in high
school, he loved to ride the rides.
Yes.  I like to ride the Ferris wheel
at the fair.  Right.  Let's go on a food trip
today, guys.
We are not Ferris whelks, are we?
You're not afraid of the Ferris wheel.  There's something
scary about the way you react to
his answer.  Mm.  Because the perisel there is not
like something that can't be adjusted, it's so fast like
that.  Why is
their hair like that?  I don't know.  I didn't do
that.  I just rode that one at the fair
.  Oh, what do you think of that
boat as a hammock?  That's not Viking, that's
Viking, then I didn't cry anymore,
I just did nothing for 3 seconds, I was stopped by something
because they thought I was being killed because I just
did that, now we're going to the
challenge of this vlog, that's the
fair, there's a challenge we talked about before
recording, he
said let's go to the fair,
let's have some games to win, there should be a first
jump, let's transition, let's
jump later, just wait,
miss is saying something, no, don't include me in the group 5,
I'm already there, what's up,
W, I'm tired, no one has fallen asleep,
no one has not played music yet,
then we should bring home a winner
from the fair, we're
all here, you
like playing fairs,
why should I play the fair, there's a game
in
Chichinalas, I'll show you the original crops,
I'm playing,
you're okay, I'm not
too old because
I don't really hang out at the fair, but you're not
kidding, because I don't have money,
I'm the one with the guns, you're the one with the
money, I didn't want to copy,
I just experienced the fair when
I was brought  Even when he goes out,
I'm not allowed to,
so you two can enjoy this, you
teacher, shs, that's all
the interest he'll learn,
even the people,
I'm not just coloring games, ever
since I was a banker, there's no one
there, he's very social, he asked you,
hey, did we go to the beach, baby, and you're
not talking about me when I was a kid, there's no
one there, I like the one at the
beach, golf, me, me, or what,
pickle, let's
just play
together, let's go to Pariah, he did
n't
say he lost here, he'll win,
the transition was so funny, I thought,
suddenly, we'll win like that, then when we get
there, we'll win, okay, okay,
this transition is so funny,
let's see if it's
effective, who's going to edit this, what's the
deal, is the transition good,
transition, okay, no need for anything, no laps,
no laps, okay.  1 2 3 go.
Including two.   There are
only two of them.
They were left behind.
Guys, the last time
I edited that vlog was during Choy's birthday
.  I am having a very hard time.
That vlog really kept me awake
today, my editor.  We will make it difficult for
him.  We'll leave first, guys.
2 3 If you weren't caught on video.  Oh,
here it is.  One more thing.  One more thing.  Here again.
What are you doing now, sister?  What are you doing now?
You edited this.  You are zero.
No coins.  No coins.  Ma'am, where is
the
Ma'am, I watched the video, where is it?
Okay.  One, two, three, go.
Very funny.
There are games here.  You guys don't want those
with ADHD here because what we're going to do
is make us fall more and more.
How many RCs?  11 guys.
This is my angle.
Does he like it?
No one cares.   My
sister doesn't have one.  Oh, sister, try it.  Try it
.
Wow.
He has so many bullets.  The videographer is being hit
.
How many points does he have?  How many is that?  14.
14. 14. Me guys.  I can turn around now.
That gun is different.  That's different.  That might
be different.  Sorry, sorry,
that one.  You are a teacher.  You are a teacher.   The
wolf's skill in handling a gun is terrible.  Why is it called chicherya?
Ah, so
you can have a baby, why are you
aborting it?
How many of you?
He is 13 years old and has a
criminology check in full.
Just wait.  The course
you took
in the middle is perfect, everything is there, everything is here,
everything is here, everything is here, don't
worry, it's not all falling off, many
falling off, it's coming along,
oh 'ba joy,
someone urinated on that, it's two points
high, 'ba ate, ah, it's two points,
because it's possible
that high, Animals, I thought
you were a designer, when did you get it?  12, one has fallen, oh
you raise your hands, hit
the one that's flushy, yeah,
okay game.   It
doesn't go away,
so
back pain
is a bullet.
Oh, your brother,
stop that.
It's okay, I really don't want to.  Hey, bad, bad.   Oh,
that's two points, yes, that's two points.   No, no
Choi, are you ready?  Okay.
I'm
not a fan of this, huh?  How are
you feeling?  That's not basic.
We are just so small.  Six six basic
kill that's
Okay.  Let's go.  First of all,
I can't be the first.  That's the first thing
.
We are behind, guys.
I have it upstairs, look at it, it's
choy choy, I'm behind you, sister, there's the
dirtiest one you've ever worn. I do
n't like it, I don't like it, I don't like
anything.
What are you doing?
You're too close to me, I
don't want you to be stabbed.
Just close your eyes.
You're with me, you're the one,
our friends left
you
here, you're here, you're here, you're here,
your sister said, how could I leave
you here, you're so lazy, you're running away, my brother, how could that be me? What's up, let's
eat.  Eat eat
Oh, what a
shame, the Vikings are closed, guys.   What a
pity, father.
That's where it ends, guys.  There are many more
great activities here in our
town.  But because we have limited time, I'm
sorry, that's all we can do right
now.  Next time.  Okay, next time.  So,
group five, don't forget to
like, comment, share, and
subscribe
to group five.
Measure.
So